let laCasaDePapleQuestions = [
	{
		question:
			'How many people did The Professor recruit to carry out the plan to occupy the Royal Mint of Spain?',
		choiceA: '8',
		choiceB: '9',
		choiceC: '10',
		choiceD: '11',
		correctAnswer: '8',
	},
	{
		question: ' Inspector Raquel’s mother suffers from what medical condition?',
		choiceA: 'Alzheimer’s Disease',
		choiceB: 'Paranoid Schizophrenia',
		choiceC: 'Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder',
		choiceD: 'Cancer',
		correctAnswer: 'Alzheimer’s Disease',
	},
	{
		question: 'How much currency does the gang print at the Royal Mint?',
		choiceA: '879 million euros',
		choiceB: '926 million euros',
		choiceC: '984 million euros',
		choiceD: '777 million euros',
		correctAnswer: '984 million euros',
	},
	{
		question: 'The Professor’s first name is eventually revealed. What is it?',
		choiceA: 'Andrés',
		choiceB: 'Aníbal',
		choiceC: 'Sergio',
		choiceD: 'Racquel',
		correctAnswer: 'Sergio',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Before giving up on society and turning to a life of crime, what was Moscow’s occupation?',
		choiceA: 'Hacker',
		choiceB: 'Soldier',
		choiceC: 'Miner',
		choiceD: 'Clerk',
		correctAnswer: 'Miner',
	},
	{
		question:
			'The show is actually called La Casa de Papel, which literally translates to what?',
		choiceA: 'The Paper House',
		choiceB: 'The Outcasts',
		choiceC: 'The House of Outcasts',
		choiceD: 'The House',
		correctAnswer: 'The Paper House',
	},
	{
		question:
			'In which country does Raquel track the Professor after the first heist?',
		choiceA: 'Philippines',
		choiceB: 'Thailand',
		choiceC: 'China',
		choiceD: 'Malaysia',
		correctAnswer: 'Philippines',
	},
	{
		question:
			'How many heists had Berlin pulled off before the event of “Money Heist”?',
		choiceA: '25',
		choiceB: '27',
		choiceC: '32',
		choiceD: '23',
		correctAnswer: '27',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Who quoted this “After all what is more human than the fight for survival ”?',
		choiceA: 'Professor',
		choiceB: 'Tokyo',
		choiceC: 'Rio',
		choiceD: 'Berlin',
		correctAnswer: 'Tokyo',
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which continent is *not* represented with a nickname among the robbers?',
		choiceA: 'Africa',
		choiceB: 'Asia',
		choiceC: 'Oceania',
		choiceD: 'Australia',
		correctAnswer: 'Oceania',
	},
];